不只是检查这里
'Cause it's not just here.
让我告诉你  抬起你的手臂
Let me show you. Raise your arms.
你是来真的吗
Are you serious?
不做给你看他是不会罢休的
He won't stop until he shows you.
这跟性无关
It's not a sex thing.
跟"救你的命"有关
It's a "Save your life" Thing.
你的肿瘤不是良性的吗
I thought your lump was benign.
我的肿瘤是良性的  但恐惧却是  却是
My lump was benign, but the scare was very, very--
该死  那个词是什么来着
shit, what is the word again?
-恶性的  -恶性的
- Malignant. - Malignant!
抬起你的手臂  菲奥娜
Raise your arms, Fiona,
因为"恶性"这个词
because "Malignant" is not a word
将是你永远都不想记起的
you ever want to have to remember.
裤子吊带脱了
Drop the overalls.
好了  不只是这里
All right. It's not just here.
还有这里  和手臂下面
It's here too, and under the arms here.
知道了吗
All right?